RAMA KRISHNA REDDY RAMIDI

Professional Title

Over 1 year of impressive track record of excellence in the banking industry, Seeking a career in the field of Supply Chain management and Operation management to utilize my knowledge and take responsibility to contribute towards the growth of Organization.



krishramidi7@gmail.com



8247356365



Hyderabad

EDUCATION

PGPM

ICFAI Business School- Mumbai

05/2019 - 03/2021

Courses

Operations Management

Bachelor of Technology

K L university

05/2015 - 04/2019

Courses

Mechanical Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deputy Manager ICICI BANK

08/2021 - Present

Managing cost, quality, and efficiency to achieve organizational growth and customer requirement. Design and management ofproducts as per the customer requirements. End-to-end operations of the customer. Ensure the system and ops level Compliances Strictly adhered. Managing Relationship with the customers pertaining to business requirements

INTERNSHIPS

Hetero Drugs (02/2020 - 06/2020)

ware house management

John Deere India private ltd

problem Identifier

Finnovation Tech Solution (01/2018 - 02/2019)

Campus Manager

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Simultaneous scheduling in a flexible manufacturing system through symbiotic organic research

CERTIFICATES

Using Databases with Python from the University of Michigan

Programming for Everybody (Getting started with python)from the University of Michigan

Supply chain management from udemy

ACHIEVEMENTS

Ranked 1st in Brand Blitz in Brahmostav at Thakur College, Mumbai (2019)

Ranked 3rd in Neuron capacitor test in Brahmostav at Thakur College, Mumbai (2019)

Best Campus Manager of Finnovation Tech solution Pvt ltd (2018)

LANGUAGES

Engilish

Telugu

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Elementary Proficiency

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVATE

Computer lab student assistantship at IBS Mumbai

Core team member of Entrepreneur cell IBS Mumbai